Ha Jung Hoon!
When are you going to marry?
When are you going to marry Hye Yoon?
I'm interested in that couple these days.
In other words, I'm worried about that couple.
Ha Jung Hoon, why aren't answering?
I know my kid is the problem.
I can't really blame you for this.
Come here, you two.
Jung Hye Yoon and Ha Jung Hoon.
Come here please.
We won't move until you two come.
Come here.
I heard something very strange a few days ago.
Somebody said she loves him but she broke up with him.
Isn't she crazy? Why did she break up with him if she loves him?
My sister, Deul Lae, finally got married with someone she loves at age 50.
There are people who take 50 years to find and marry with someone they love.
These two must be crazy.
Please hold each other's hand.
Put your hands up.
I went to somebody's wedding a while ago and the bride gave three cheers.
The two of you should give three cheers in front of us as an apology.
What are you doing? Where is the cheers?
Hurray. Hurray. Hurray.
Kiss. Kiss. Kiss.
When everyone wants to do it, then you should at least pretend to do it.
When do you think you can kiss in front of many people. This is a chance.
Please enjoy your meal
You guys can eat now.
People con't like if the congratulatory message is wrong. Enjoy your food.
This was a very nice congratulatory message from Lee Deul Ja.
Food is prepared over there. Feel free to help yourself.
They should be able to get back together now.
-I'm sorry.
-For what?
She made people there misunderstand our relationship.
It's okay. That's her charm.
You guys must be so embarrassed.
That was so funny.
MY employees took pictures of that and want to upload the video on Youtube.
I already did. I hope it can get many hits so my homepage gets popular.
Are you making money by selling us?
I'm sorry. I'll treat you if I make a lot of money out of it. You too, Hye Yoon.
I didn't know you'd help my mom.
It's funny.
Hye Yoon, your mom is so funny.
I'm embarrassed.
Stop it.
This reminds me of the old times.
Do you remember when the four of us went to a trip together?
When?
Two years ago. When we went to ski at Young Pyung. You guys came late so we were stuck on the road for 8 hours.
We weren't late. Jung Hoon and I were never late.
We always came on time.
It was Gi Joong who came late.
We were never late.
- Yeah, we weren't late.
- Yeah, we...
Why?
Nothing.
Hye Yoon.
Unconsciously, I called us "we".
You know what...
I still have an inferiority complex.
My mom is still the same.
So is the reality.
But I missed you.
I missed you so much.
I regretted it.
I want to go back.
But I don't know how...
You can come back like this.
Episode 17.
- Give him to me.
- I'll put him in his room.
I hope you are doing this because you want to.
If you are doing this because of the custody don't do it. It will hurt his feeling.
He's my kid. I didn't pay much attention to him because you were with him.
But you will be gone soon.
The plaintiff is financially competent and intellectual ability
will provide a sound environment for the child
What are you making?
I am thinking about making dumplings
You're surely trying to get me annoyed. The menu changes everyday
It was like that before. You just didn't notice it because you weren't interested
Your sister and Junghoon broke up
Junghoon didn't even tell me about it
Because he is considerate
Your mom is still the same
Her and her tricks trying to marry off Junghoon with your sister. She was the same with me and you
Even if I try, I cannot think nicely of you
why do you keep on picking on my mom?
Am I doing this for no reason? Look at her today how she's trying to make Junghoon marry your sister
Old habits die hard
I guess you really didn't want to marry me but you were forced into it
That's why you hate my mom because she had us get married
Let's finalize the divorce process in a hurry
Give me the custody
Then I will try to agree to your terms regarding division of assets
How can I trust you to give you custody? The beast inside of you could bite my son.
Stop using that! The beast
It's my second day wearing this
Do I have to be chased out like this?
What are you doing here?
Where are my shirts?
Look for it. It must be somewhere
I've already seen everything. What are you trying to hide?
You've seen everything?
You're so easy
From these things, I think your lawyer is better than my lawyer
It's illegal to copy family inspector's report, but he got it done
But he will lose because of you
Not being thorough, leaving it out like this
It's too early to judge
what do you mean early?
You could tell how the end result would be from its steps.
You will lose in the end.
I feel better. I was a bit worried since the law favors mother for custody of a child.
Now I could rest assured.
Let's never let go of each other.
Thank you for waiting for me.
Thank you for coming.
I am sorry for leaving you when I would come back like this.
If you love someone, you become vulnerable to that someone you love.
Quite a few times, I felt vulnerable to you too. The things you lack felt overly big because you love me.
So don't feel apologetic about it.
I think I found where I belong.
I wish time would stop like this.
-It's cold.
-Yes
It will get warmer soon.
I wish I could stay with you more.
What you wanted to do before, should we do it?
A woman full of lust.
-Can't we?
-We can.
I learned how much I love you when I was apart from you.
Why do we only realize such important thing when we are apart?
I learned I should never give up on this love no matter what.
Do you want some tea?
- No, I'm going home.
- Why did you walk me home anyway?
I want to do what other men do for their girlfriend.
Why? You don't like it?
I like it but I'm kind of nervous.
What are you nervous about?
It feels kind of weird to be protected by somebody.
I like the feeling of protecting somebody.
Would Hye Yoon and Jung Hoon get back together?
- I don't know.
- You're saying it like it's not your business.
- It isn't.
- Here we go again.
By the way, I still feel awkward with them. I feel like there's a wall between them and I.
That's good! The distance between you and them was too close.
Why did you become so mature?
You were a jerk before.
- A jerk?
- Yeah, a jerk.
Do you want to see a real jerk?
Yeah, I do.
Come to my house early in the morning. Show me your marketing plan.
- Why do I have to go to your house?
- I have to go to Busan.
I want to see you before I go there.
It's warm.
I know.
Wait.
Should I lift you up?
It's okay. Your back might get hurt like last time.
Okay then. I feel like I lived with you for a long time.
Me too. I can't even imagine the time you were gone in my life.
- Do you want to take a shower first?
- No.
Then can I take one first?
Are there only two ways to take a shower?
You're a dirty woman.
Let's take a shower together.
- Aren't you sleeping?
- I'm not sleepy.
- Let's have a fight sometimes.
- Why?
We never had a fight since we start dating.
- Isn't it weird?
- I don't want to fight.
I had every fight that I can have in my life during my other married life.
But we are too compatible with each other. Isn't it so weird?
No, it's not.
Yes, it is weird. How is that possible?
It is but that's because we are weird.
Yeah, we are weird.
- Yeah.
- Let's sleep.
- I'm going to call my sister before I sleep.
- Why?
I didn't call her after the reception.
You care about her too much and are scared of her too much.
This house is kind of unfamiliar to me.
You're not unfamiliar to me but this house is.
I think I feel better if I hear her voice.
Okay.
Why isn't Hye Yoon coming back yet?
Holy cow.
Hello!
- Unnie.
- Why did you call me? Aren't you sleeping?
- It's weird.
- What is?
- I'm not in my house.
- Of course, you aren't.
You got married.
I think I got married too fast.
You're crazy. Getting married at the age of 50 is too fast?
For some people, they can marry twice in 50 years.
I wasn't talking about that. She's so mean.
Are you not coming in? It feels weird without you.
I'm not calling my sister anymore.
You're my family.
- I'm happy to have a family.
- Me too. I finally have my own family.
A husband and a wife.
I can't help it.
Let's get crazy tonight.
I will be free once Hye Yoon gets married.
- Why aren't you coming home?
- I am now.
- Were you in front of the house?
- Yeah.
Where did you during the dinner time? Jung Hoon left, too.
You're very insightful. Did you see everything?
Of course, I did. Who do you think I did that for in front of so many people?
It was for you and Jung Hoon.
My tentacle was following you and him but while eating you guys were gone.
- Were you with him?
- No.
- Then where have you been?
- Here and there.
Didn't you feel anything seeing your aunt getting married?
Getting married is nothing. They did it too quickly.
We were going to do it but who interfered it?
We didn't have enough money.
Min Ho isn't that good looking but he got a lot of money.
It's not hard if a man got a money.
He didn't want anything from her.
If you don't change the way you think, I can't marry him.
Then are you going to marry him if I pay exactly half for the wedding?
How can you do that? You don't have money.
I can't ruin my family for my wedding.
Then what do you want to do?
Are you not going to do anything about it? Didn't Jung Hoon say anything?
I'll talk to you later.
I'm really happy now. I want to feel this happiness by myself.
They got back together.
She must be embarrassed.
Because the sensible lost to the senseless.
Hey.
Are you home?
Yeah. I got home. I just took off my shoes.
- It was a good timing.
- Yeah.
- You just go home?
Who are you talking on the phone?
Hye Yoon.
Hye Yoon?
It's Mom. I told her I'm on the phone with you.
Then come by my office. Let's watch a movie.
Good. I haven't watch any movie since I broke up with you.
Me, too.
Buy the tickets. You have time to do that since it's vacation, right?
What are you talking about? Hye Yoon?
I'm on the phone!
She sounds mad. I heard her.
So are you going to run away again?
No.
Good night.
Okay. Good night.
Don't be afraid. I understand her.
Let's take a shower and sleep.
You're coming so rude. Why did you yell at me while I'm on the phone?
Because I was so shocked.
You guys got back together?
- Yeah.
- I can't believe this.
Is a marriage a joke?
She told us to our face that she broke up with you.
Like she's not going to see us at all.
- Are you going to do this again?
- Do what?
Ruining our relationship.
I didn't ruin it. It was ruined because it wasn't strong enough.
It's not going to be ruined this time. We learned our lesson.
Son, but I can't let it happen this time.
What?
I was very happy about the break up in my mind.
Since you met her, the peace in our family is gone and war came in.
Your father never yelled at me but he did because of her.
I will never forget that.
So?
Are you going to marry her?
We didn't talk about it yet.
I'm telling you this now. Listen very carefully.
Don't marry her. I will oppose it greatly.
Why?
If you really love her, you can date her. I won't stop you.
I liked her when you were just dating. The problem started after she became your fiance.
You can see or date her. But don't marry her.
When are you going to marry him?
You knew?
Of course, I did. You're a so sensible woman.
Stop it, Mom. It's embarrassing.
You feel embarrassed?
Who made that happen?
You did.
This breakfast is for my senseless mother who won over her sensible daughter.
Stop doing it. Do it fast now. There's nothing to worry about now.
Give your parents-in-law the bottom drawer.
I will talk to Mrs. Ha.
We haven't talk about the marriage yet.
We only confirmed that we still love each other.
Do you have to do that? You should know that already.
She canceled the wedding hall. I can't marry him right away.
You can't marry because there's no wedding hall? You worry too much.
Anyway, don't meet her until I talk to Mr. and Mrs. Ha.
Alright.
So, you're listening to me now? How shocking.
I didn't say I'm not going to. I only said alright.
Mom.
Hey.
You don't have fever. Are you really sick?
Yes, I am.
What's wrong? You were okay last night.
Please promise me one thing.
- What is it?
- Don't ask. You must promise.
If you promise me one thing, I'd feel so much better.
- I will promise.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
- Give me my phone.
Why do you need that?
I do know if you promise something, you keep that promise.
But this promise is very important.
Just in case you change your mind, I want you to record it.
I, Ha Dong Geon, will keep the promise with my wife, Park Eun Young.
Repeat after me.
If I don't, I'm a hypocrite.
Why are you making me do this?
Are you not going to do it? I'm sick.
If I don't, I'm a hypocrite. Are you happy now?
- Yes, I am.
- Tell me.
Jung Hoon and Hye Yoon got back together.
Really? That's good!
Are you kidding me?
What I want you to promise is that...
you will not take any side when I try to stop him from getting married to her.
Don't take any side!
- Between who and who?
- Between Jung Hoon and I.
I'm going to oppose him from getting married to her.
Honey.
I'm not asking you to side with me.
Keep the promise. You promised me.
Honey, that's...
If I don't, I'm a hypocrite.
I heard you're sick. Are you okay?
I'm okay.
- Dad.
- Yes?
- I'm seeing Hye Yoon again.
- I heard that.
I'm sorry for changing my mind back and forth.
But this is how people grow. Please understand me.
Sure. Let's eat.
I'm going to meet Hye Yoon and talk about our marriage again.
You canceled the wedding hall, right?
Yeah, she canceled it.
Why do you ask your dad about this and not to me?
Because I feel comfortable talking to him. What about the apartment?
I put that up for a rent. There isn't a place and a wedding hall for you now.
So, you can't get married this year.
If you want to marry, do it after two years. After the contract for the apartment is done.
That means you're planning to stop me. You said that last night.
I know you're trying to stop me. That's just
an excuse. I'm not breaking up with her.
Do whatever you want to. I'm going
to do whatever I want to do, too.
Dad, please stop her.
I don't know why she's doing that.
- I'm sorry. I promised her.
- What?
To not to take any side on your marriage.
So, don't ask for my help.
You see?
He and I already talked about it.
It's my marriage.
If I want to do it, I can.
Hye Yoon's mother thinks the same as I do.
When I met her the last time, we already talked about it.
Do you think you can live with Hye Yoon happily when your parents don't want you to?
We will find out if I can or not after I live with her.
I won't give up on things that I haven't even try.
Jung Hoon!
What he said is right.
I want you to stay neutral, not judge us.
You should hire a native of Busan.
They can communicate with customers better.
I will.
You go to Busan from here back and forth. But you're the boss. You should stay there.
Are you going to stay in Busan?
I have someone I can trust there.
I know I came too early.
I stopped by before I go on my exercise.
This is my mother.
Hello.
Why is she here this early time?
- Did she sleep here?
- No, I came for business.
I'm working as a marketing planner for his business.
Really? But you shouldn't come to his house this early.
I will leave now. It was almost done anyway.
Mr. Gong, I'll go now. Give me a call later.
Where are you going?
Mom, she's my girlfriend, Dong Bi.
Your girlfriend?
Since when?
We broke up after five years of dating. We just started dating again a few days ago.
Why did you say you work for him?
I thought you'd get mad if I tell you I'm his girlfriend.
Nice catch. You date him and work at the same time?
He hired me so I can make some money.
I hate a woman who sponge off her boyfriend.
You don't have to worry about it. He would never be used by a woman.
While he dated me, we always split the bills.
Maybe he doesn't love you.
If a man loves a woman, he opens his wallet for her.
I didn't know that. Thank you for telling me.
I shouldn't pay for anything next time I see him.
Actually, I'm poor. The business I have is about to fail, too.
But you look a little bit too arrogant.
Should you be respectful toward me?
You talk back at everything I say. I don't like that.
Honestly, I'm scared to talk to you now so I'm trying to keep calm myself.
And that makes me talk too much.
It's hard to be honest in front of me. What does your father do?
I'm abandoned by my family.
So you're being confident but not because of your background, huh?
You can date my son if you want to.
But, you can't marry him.
Okay. Goodbye.
I'm going to walk her out.
Don't you see me? Walk her out only to the door.
No. I'm going to walk her home.
You said you have to go to Busan.
- It can wait.
- Then what about me?
What do you want to do?
Do you want to come with us or stay here?
What are you trying to tell me now?
I'm here. Where are you going?
Mom, you're not a kid anymore. Decide what you're going to do.
You'll regret what you're doing.
Why are you dating a worthless girl?
Are you filming a movie now? What are you doing?
Let's go.
Hey, Gong Gi Joong!
- Are you going to be okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm scared.
Jung Hoon's mother is scary, too. She's Jung Hoon's mother's sister, right?
All married women are scary. I don't want to get married if I think about that.
You shouldn't go further.
It's my mom.
I'm healing myself. I'm trying to be honest with everybody you know.
- You can go back. I'll go by myself.
- No. I'll walk you home.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
Why?
Why did you say yes when my mom told you to only date me not marry me?
You aren't planning to marry me either.
I can change my mind.
What do you mean?
Marry me.
- No.
- Why?
Your mom is scary.
You only see me and I only see you. That's a marriage.
It's going to one direction together.
You still don't want to?
I'm scared to be a part of a family you know.
Like you said, I ran away from my family because I couldn't handle it.
My heart isn't healthy yet.
Me neither. My heart is full of wounds.
I'm afraid, too.
You are? You're Gong Gi Joong.
Yeah. This is the first time that I thought of living a life with someone I love.
I'm afraid because I'm not sure if I can do it.
Why didn't we talk about this earlier?
I feel like we are one step closer to each other.
Me, too.
Sorry.
- Want to come in?
- No, I should get going.
- But think about it.
- What?
My proposal.
Did you propose to me?
I did at the elevator.
Oh, was it a proposal? I didn't know.
- Get in.
- Bye.
- Call me as you go.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
Mom.
If you keep doing things like this, you will lose your son.
It's a warning.
Let's have lunch together. I can't wait anymore.
- You made all this?
- Yeah.
It's what we usually eat but it take times to make it.
- I can't believe it.
- What?
That you can make food.
You saw me cooking before.
Do you know a poem called ' I miss you even if you're with me'?
- I do.
- That's exactly how I feel.
Me too. I must've been crazy. Why did I break up with you?
We realized how much we love each other while we were away.
You're right.
Let's go to my house tonight. We should talk to my parents about it.
- Your mom doesn't like me, does she?
- Yeah, she doesn't.
What should I do?
It's our problem. We're going to live together. She will understand us.
Unless you run away.
I'm not running away.
What do you want to do about the wedding? I want to do it. I know I don't have money.
But I can make money you know. I think this is the right time for us to marry.
- Let's do it then.
- Good. Let's do it.
I have to go back to the office soon. What are you going to do?
I will be heading over to Dong Bi's office.
Are you okay with her?
That's a hard thing to do. I got hurt from her once. It takes times to recover it.
We are okay outwardly but there's still a wound in my heart.
I looked them through and fixed what I can do.
You didn't have to hurry. Why did you finish it so quickly?
I want you to remember my sincerity.
My father's company isn't related to me.
That's what everybody says. They said they don't care.
But would they really? Did you have a fight with Hye Yoon?
Stop trying it. Hye Yoon won't change her mind.
You don't know about women. First love aren't that easily forgotten.
Do you know how your name
appears on her phone?
- What is it?
- 'You're out'.
- What?
- Oppa, you're out a long time ago.
I can be in again. Don't frighten me.
I should get going. I have to go to the court with Hye Jin.
- Hye Yoon.
- Oppa!
We are meant to be. How can we meet like this coincidentally?
Just go. You said today is Hye Jin's trial.
- Is it?
- Yeah. Want to come with me?
It's good to learn about a divorce before you get married.
- Why does she have to go? Come in.
- No. I think it's a good idea.
I investigated on his bank account.
What's that investigation for?
It's like you requested facts that you wanted the court to know.
Then we can use the facts as an evidence.
We can't reach the National Tax Service individually.
A lot of money in his account was taken out into another account.
I'm going to ask the court to look into whose account it belongs to.
It's probably Yuri's.
That's even better.
Hye Yoon also came.
I thought you'd be careless about this kind of stuff.
I told her to come.
It's an educational experience.
Hye Yoon will get married eventually. It'd be good for her to know about a divorce.
Anyway it's a good thing that you can learn something from my divorce.
It'd be good if she can learn good things out of it, and not bad things.
Don't you think so?
You clenched your fist.
I've seen this face a lot. My face usually calls for fists.
But they know they can't punch me so they clenched their fist instead.
- Stop it.
- I didn't do anything. I only talked.
- Come in.
- Let's go.
We requested a breakdown of Jeon Hye Jin's credit card usage.
We got them from Wuin bank and Tae Yang bank.
But not from Chang Shin bank.
As for the breakdown of Nam Do Hyun's tax and bank account...
we are all having hard times but we're overcoming them in our own ways.
According to your logic, I deserve this.
We got them from Ahseo bank and Shin Han bank.
From the insurance company, only Kimhae insurance company hasn't still given us that.
Your honor, please give us the permission for the child psychological test.
- Is that test what you talked about before?
- Yeah.
The plaintiff has a better financial means for the kid.
Since the kid is a boy, it'd be better for him to be raised by his father.
Also, the defendant's mother is very unusual and she doesn't have enough money to raise the kid...
I think it's right for him to raise him.
Can't you argue about what she said?
It won't do anything good.
We looked through the the plaintiff's Tae Yang bank statement.
The money from that bank was withdrawn without any purpose.
How did he know that?
Unless, he can see it's a borrowed-name bank account.
I'd like to request the fact of where he used that money.
Whose account is that?
Is it the woman's?
You can request any fact you want today.
As for the custody, we will proceed with the psychological test.
We will see you next time then.
I will let you know the date for the next time.
I read the officer's opinion. Thanks to you.
Sure. I made a copy of it for you to read it.
My mother is unusual and don't have enough money to raise the kid?
It's true. What can Tae Hyun possibly learn from her?
Does my mother raise him? I raise him.
No matter how hard I try, she will get the custody.
The opinion won't change anything.
If you think that way, it's just your moral victory.
Didn't you forget that Jung Hye Jin has liability reasons?
You can't make her guilty using the evidence you have.
But the evidence we have makes Nam Do Hyun guilty.
Just request for settlement money. It will be your loss anyway.
The door to us is always opened.
That's what I want to say to you. Convince her. She will not be in it.
If you think the custody as a little game, you shouldn't get the custody.
If you're really his father before the law come in.
That's a personal attack.
If this is the personal attack, I get that everyday and much worst than that.
You're working so hard tracing my bank accounts.
We should work hard we can get the money.
If you were Hye Yoon's brother-in-law, we could've been a family.
I'll be nice to you.
Let's go.
What the hell?
I'm sorry.
For what?
I didn't know it's this hard.
I didn't want you to know about this.
If there's a way you cannot get hurt, you should take that way.
How can I live a life without getting hurt?
Since Hye Yoon came with us, I'll buy you dinner.
Oppa, it's not dinner time yet. I'll treat you guys tea. Let's go.
Cool.
Hi, Mrs. Ha.
Don't call me like that.
Hi, how are you?
Good.
You heard about Jung Hoon and Hye Yoon, right?
I think we need to plan for the measures.
Of course, I do.
- I'll go there.
- Yes.
Things are looking great.
I should do something.
Maybe I should give her the bottom drawer.
Hello. Good to see you again.
I know. I already ordered your drink.
It' good to see you. I will see you more often from now but I brought a present today too.
What present? I better get this over with
Mrs. Lee. We've talked and took action about many things for our kids.
she's rambling on
she just needs to say she's happy that our kids are getting married
I think I am off to a good start. Look at her expression
So that means it's alright
Yes.
I heard from Junghoon last night that he's dating Haeyoon again.
I heard the news as well.
-Does this make sense?
-Why not?
We've reached the final destination last time. That it's over between the two families.
The kids love each other. I told you then before too. What's important are the kids.
I told you then too. That you cannot ignore family matters.
Does that mean my family is something you could ignore?
No, that's not what I am saying. You're putting in a tight spot with your straight talk.
Since you are saying you are in a tight spot, I must be right then.
I don't want the kids to date again.
Even though I didn't tell you this before, to be honest,
After deciding Haeyoon to be my daughter-in-law, many troubles found its way into my family.
Life is full of troubles. That's normal.
I guess you didn't have a normal life before.
Freeze, I am about to lose again.I need to give that final blow today.
Yes. No one makes trouble in my family so I led a peaceful life.
It seems like you're the troublemaker
I thought you have class, highly educated, pretty, have good character. Every time we had a conversation,
Wait.
I shouldn't talk to much. I get roped into her.
Just end the discussion.
You cut me off.
Everytime I talk to you, I could never win.
I lose my mind and get roped into it.
I say what I shouldn't say. I don't get to say what I want to say. Just to sum it up.
I cannot agree to their marriage.
Good job. I just need to talk to Haeyoon now.
Mrs. You left this behind.
You're very good at your job. You were cool.
Why all of a sudden? You always knew I was good at my job.
I knew it. But it's different when I actually see you doing it.
I feel so secure that you're working on my case.
Any shortcomings I have, I blow them away with my talk.
Being a lawyer is my calling.
It seems like it.
It's nice to have someone like me as your family.
I know. Your spouse will be lucky to have you.
I need to use the washroom.
Please give me your cell phone.
Haeyoon. Sangjin Out.
It's true. I'm out?
Yes. There is a side of you when you dumped me.
It's true. I understand.
What are you doing?
I will be your "in" from now in.
Sangjin.
I am dating him again.
What?
Why?
I can't seem to get over him.
So, you should meet a nice man too.
-A nice man?
-Sorry, my mistake.
A good woman.
What's so great about him? You weren't this way after we broke up.
Think this over again. You haven't seen me in court and decided to get back together with him.
You saw me before. You said I am cool.
You look cool at your job only.
Suddenly, one of my goal is gone.
-I feel dejected.
-I kept on telling you that this wasn't working for me.
I got it. My motto is I don't try to get together with someone who's taken.
So it's you who's rejecting me. Since I am taken.
Are you trying to pity me?
Yes, Mother-in-law.
Yes. I got it.
Yes.
Sanjin, I need to get going. If my sister comes back, tell her I had to leave first.
Hey.
Is this me rejecting you? It's you rejecting me.
Look at her smiling.
I don't want to stay single for Christmas.
Please turn off the Christmas carol.
Mother-in-law.
Have a seat.
-Would you like something to drink?
-You could drink.
I just had a drink when I met your mother.
-You met my mom?
-I asked to meet her.
Haeyoon.
I've given this a lot of thought.
I am amazed at myself for being able to do such a thing.
But what can I do? This is about my kid.
What is this about?
Please break up with Junghoon. You guys are not meant to be.
If you were meant to be together, it wouldn't be rocky. You guys are rocky.
You saw what happened to Kijoong's marriage when he didn't have it rocky.
Mother-in-law. It wasn't easy for me to decide to get back together with Junghoon.
Because Junghoon and I went through the rocky journey together.
We learned how to cherish each other.
Mother-in-law, please accept me.
I am sorry. I could accept if it's you alone.
I went through the rocky phases with your mother during wedding preparation. I cannot accept your mother.
You are planning to meeti Junghoon later today and come to my place in the evening.
Please don't. I don't want to get into an argument with my son.
Hurry. Come.
Tada.
Where did you get this?
I bought it. At the used motorcycle shop you sold it to.
I really like him.
Exactly. After meeting me, I want you to be happy, doing things that you like.
I don't want you to give up anything because of me.
What's wrong? Did I do something?
No. I am wondering if it's okay for me to be this happy.
Even if I die now, I won't regret anything.
Don't even joke about such things.
I love you, Lee Deul Rae.
- Why are you late?
- I met your mother.
It started again. Same as before.
We have to respond differently.
I am so upset.
I am sorry.
I am wavering again. I was so sure until yesterday.
Don't let go.
I know.
-Father-in-law.
-Welcome, it's good to see you.
Please have some of this. I heard you like this.
-Yes, I like waffles
-We bought it from your favorite shop.
-Thank you.
-Where is mom?
Please take a seat. We need to tell you something.
I've already said everything that needs to be said.
When?
I heard you already met Haeyoon.
You told him everything? When I asked you not to?
I learned marriage is not just coming together of two people but two families.
But the most important thing is the union between two people, not two families.
You're saying that because you haven't lived in this world long enough.
Then from now on, I will learn as I live. For now, it's Haeyoon.
I am not just talking about the family. I am sorry to say this to your face.
-I don't like Haeyoon.
-Mom.
Honey.
How long has it been since she told us that she broke up with Junghoon?
She may say she's firm about marrying Junghoon.
she will give up if some difficulty arises.
Do you know how important marriage is in a man's life?
I saw many man's life go down the drain after marrying the wrong girl.
I only have one son.
At first, I didn't know better and said I am fine with whomever my son likes.
What happened afterwards? Family was turned upside down.
This was even before they were married. What do you think will happen once they are actually married?
I have a responsibility and right to keep the peace for my son and my family.
Haeyoon. Please give like, like you did before. Let my son go.
I am sorry, Haeyoon. I apologize on her behalf.
I know no words could provide comfort now.
Junghoon, please comfort her.
I will take you home. Let's go.
-You must be very upset.
-Yes.
I am by your side. Insult to you is insult to me as well.
It's true that we didn't earn our parent's trust in the process of wedding preparation,
I guess that's because it's our first time getting married.
Why is it always hard for us?
So we could love each other for a long time for the rest of our lives. It's making us stronger.
What is this?
It's Haeyoon's wedding present(dowry)
I heard they're back together. You want to give it to the in-laws tomorrow?
I brought it to give to Mrs. Ha, but I couldn't even talk about this.
- Why?
- She got knock out on this round.
What are you talking about?
She knocked me out and left.
This is why people should live long.
You really can't think badly of me.
So why did you say things you can't even handle?
There was no other way.
Jung Hoon and Hye Yoon shouldn't be together.
She's too controlling.
I can't see him getting controlled by Hye Yoon and her mother for the rest of his life.
Did you drop Hye Yoon off?
I called a cab for her.
Why are you looking at me like that?
This is the lowest I have seen you be. Are you that kind of person?
What about me?
You're heartless and cruel. Is it alright to hurt someone's precious daughter saying this is for the sake of my kid?
When you're like that, you instructed me till now to live an upright life?
This is all for you.
I've told you many times, if it's for my sake, just let me do what I want!
Even if I fail, its my failure. I will take the responsibility for my failure.
I can't watch you fail in your marriage, of all things.
Do you know how soft hearted men are? They become even softer as they get older.
Even your father, who seemed so strong, came clean a while ago. Men are more weak mentally.
It's the woman who can control that.
That's why the marriage is important to a man.
I can't get through to you. You just keep on repeating importance of the marriage to a man.
If you continue to be like this, then I have no choice but to marry Hye Yoon on our own.
Fine, leave and live together with her.
- Don't be like this
- Dad, mom is not normal.
Jung Hoon, even if your mom may not be normal, I have to side with her.
Wife is more important than a son.
Why do I feel more betrayed by you?
I am so upset really.
I don't want our kids to date again.
Hye Yoon is sleeping over at Dong Bi's. She's not coming.
- She's probably really upset.
- Do you think Mrs. Ha said something to her?
She does it to me, of course she will do it to Hye Yoon too.
Family background? What does it mean to come from a nice family background? She doesn't even have a nice personality to say You are not it to their face.
What should we do? It seems like kids have assurance about each other now.
If the kids are assured, we have to support them.
Even if I end it, I can't end it like this. We need to properly battle it out.
Yes?
I've thought long, I think we still have unfinished business.
We should meet up. When are you free?
I have to go to the realtors in the morning, afternoon would be good.
- You're here, madam.
- Yes, I am not late, am I?
The new tenant isn't here yet.
Really?
But madam, your apartment in Gangnam, did you put it on the market?
No, why do you ask?
No, an Ahjumma came to see the house.
I never put it on the market.
Who came to see the house?
- She must have gotten in confused with another unit.
- I don't think it was a mistake.
She said Head Doctor.
Really? That's odd.
I will ask the Head Doctor.
Other than Gangbook, you don't own an apartment in Gangnam?
- Please sit.
- Let's
What would you like to drink? I didn't order any tea.
I just heard the weirdest thing now.
What do you mean?
It's a ridiculous thing and such thing shouldn't happen. It just doesn't make any sense.
It's common sense again. I guess she shares something with Hye Yoon. That brat was talking about common sense too.
Stop saying it doesn't make sense and tell me what it is. What doesn't make sense?
- Hye Yoon's mother
- Yes.
How did you find out we own an apartment in Gangnam?
Why do you ask this suddenly?
I never told you I knew about it.
Someone was running a background check on my family. I found out who she is.
Who is she?